(Penny:)I know. Then you'll finally stop
talking about it!
(Howard:)Ready to go?
Let's do this.
Have fun, guys!
(Leonard:)We will.
I can't believe Sheldon gave this up.
(Caption:)I know.
(Leonard:)We're gonna have
so much more fun than him.
(singsongy):
No, they're not.
(Penny:)Knowing them, they will.
(indistinct chatter)
T minus 15 minutes!
(Raj:)Oh, did you hear
from Wil?
(Leonard:)Yeah, he's on his way.
Time for bladder check.
(Sheldon:)Check.
(Howard:)Check. Wait.
(Howard:)Screw it. I'm holding it.
(crowd booing)
(Raj:)What is everyone
booing at?
(booing continues)
(Wil:)Hey, guys. What's up?
(Leonard:)Um, hey, Wil.
What you doin'?
I was on Star Trek. I'm just
rooting for the home team.
MAN:
Star Trek stinks!
(Wil:)Yeah? Live long
and suck it!